Inside the archaic lane I passed by
穿过了小巷后的古街
Saw you were glowing in the sunlight
青墙旁你遥望夕阳斜
The way you and I caught at first sight
只因是不经意的一瞥
Disturbed my mind every single night
扰乱我思绪不舍昼夜
Wish I could fly like a butterfly
想化作庄周变成蝴蝶
Anytime I'll be right by your side
驾青云穿过繁枝茂叶
My love's as river deep mountain high
纵然是群山层层叠叠
There ain't no way I can take my time
也无心在此流连停歇
Lay under the moonlight
将相思寄明月
Pray you not to think twice
期盼你能察觉
On our page we gong write
将你写作诗阕
I'll pray through the night
送千里无邪
You're like the stars that light up my sky
你就是梦浸白了新月
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
你就是风染红了枫叶
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
You got my heart and soul electrified
你就是泪浸白了初雪
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
You cast a shadow right on my life
你就是你染红了岁月
Take all the rays of light to another side
改变我黑白而无言的世界
Like standing on the end of a line
如溪水潺潺淌过古街
Pride's hanging on the edge of your lies
带走了如梦般的时节
Despite of all the times that I've tried
小桥上人潮络绎不绝
You've fought so hard to keep me in line
牵引我思绪层出不迭
I'll give you all that I have inside
若不识梁祝变成蝴蝶
I'll take you down to the paradise
驾紫烟穿过天上宫阙
My feelings for you can't be disguised
绝不知人间多愁离别
I'm not the one you should left behind
吹落叶散作秋风清切
Pray under the moonlight
将相思寄明月
It takes time to get right
心缱绻意难决
Will never compromise
将此情置长夜
Till stars come aline
似繁星明灭
You're like the stars that light up my sky
你就是梦浸白了新月
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
你就是风染红了枫叶
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
You got my heart and soul electrified
你就是泪浸白了初雪
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
You cast a shadow right on my life
你就是你染红了岁月
Take all the rays of light to another side
改变我黑白而无言的世界
You're like the stars that light up my sky
你就是梦浸白了新月
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
你就是风染红了枫叶
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
You got my heart and soul electrified
你就是泪浸白了初雪
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
You cast a shadow right on my life
你就是你染红了岁月
Take all the rays of light to another side
改变我黑白而无言的世界